The only person you need to be is yourself.
Save the Last Dance is a drama, family, romance film directed by Thomas Carter.
After the death of her mother, Sara moves to the South Side of Chicago to live
with her father and gets transferred to a majority-black school.
Her life takes a turn for the better when befriends Chenille and her
brother Derek, who helps her with her dancing skills.
Sara Johnson, played by Julia Stiles.
Derek Reynolds, played by Sean Patrick Thomas.
Chenille Reynolds, played by Kerry Washington.
Malakai, played by Fredro Starr.
Roy Johnson, played by Terry Kinney.
Nikki, played by Bianca Lawson.
Save the Last Dance is a 2001 American dance film produced by MTV Films,
directed by Thomas Carter and distributed by Paramount Pictures.
The film stars Julia Stiles and Sean Patrick Thomas as a teenage interracial couple in Chicago who
work together to help Stiles's character train for a Juilliard School dance audition.
Released theatrically in the United States on January 12, 2001,
the film received mixed reviews from critics.
It was a box-office success and grossed $131.5 million
worldwide against a $13 million budget.
A direct-to-video sequel, Save the Last Dance 2, was released in 2006.
The film explores themes of ballet dancer, musical, ballet.
The tone is emotional.